<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Fealess Geek Media</title><link>https://fearlessgeekmedia.com/portfolio/logos/</link><description>Recent content on Fealess Geek Media</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>2023</copyright><atom:link href="https://fearlessgeekmedia.com/portfolio/logos/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Fearless Geek Media Logo logo</title><link>https://fearlessgeekmedia.com/portfolio/logos/fearless-geek-media-logo/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://fearlessgeekmedia.com/portfolio/logos/fearless-geek-media-logo/</guid><description>Fearless Geek Media Logo This is the original Fearless Geek Media logo. I&amp;rsquo;ve since updated the logo, as you see.
I liked how casual the text was and I felt it was friendly to new clients. However, I dont&amp;rsquo; feel this exactly expressed who I am. I&amp;rsquo;m a geek. The logo itself showed that, but the text didn&amp;rsquo;t.
With the new logo that you see throughout the website, I&amp;rsquo;ve added a little more color to it, and added a terminal-style font.</description><content>
&lt;figure class="center" >
&lt;img src="https://fearlessgeekmedia.com/portfolio-images/logos/fearless-geek-media-logo.png" style="border-radius: 8px; width:500px" />
&lt;figcaption class="center" >Fearless Geek Media Logo&lt;/figcaption>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;p>This is the original Fearless Geek Media logo. I&amp;rsquo;ve since updated the logo, as you see.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I liked how casual the text was and I felt it was friendly to new clients. However, I dont&amp;rsquo; feel this exactly expressed who I am. I&amp;rsquo;m a geek. The logo itself showed that, but the text didn&amp;rsquo;t.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>With the new logo that you see throughout the website, I&amp;rsquo;ve added a little more color to it, and added a terminal-style font. Can you get much more geeky than going to a terminal style? In fact, this whole website is in a terminal style.&lt;/p></content></item><item><title>Henderson Brothers Plumbing logo</title><link>https://fearlessgeekmedia.com/portfolio/logos/hb-plumbing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://fearlessgeekmedia.com/portfolio/logos/hb-plumbing/</guid><description>Henderson Brothers Plumbing Logo This is a fictional business. I created this logo to use on an example business card design. With it being a plumbing business, I used pipes to make the H and B, and put “Henderson Bros” on the wrench.</description><content>
&lt;figure class="left" >
&lt;img src="https://fearlessgeekmedia.com/portfolio-images/logos/hb-plumbing.png" style="border-radius: 8px; width:500px" />
&lt;figcaption class="center" >Henderson Brothers Plumbing Logo&lt;/figcaption>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;p>This is a fictional business. I created this logo to use on an example business card design. With it being a plumbing business, I used pipes to make the H and B, and put “Henderson Bros” on the wrench.&lt;/p></content></item><item><title>Merrytown Dentistry Logo</title><link>https://fearlessgeekmedia.com/portfolio/logos/merrytown-dental/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://fearlessgeekmedia.com/portfolio/logos/merrytown-dental/</guid><description>Merrytown Dentistry Logo Merrytown Dental is a fictional densitry firm that I created both a website and logo for.</description><content>
&lt;figure class="center" >
&lt;img src="https://fearlessgeekmedia.com/portfolio-images/logos/merrytown-dentistry-logo.png" style="border-radius:8px, width:500px" />
&lt;figcaption class="center" >Merrytown Dentistry Logo&lt;/figcaption>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;p>Merrytown Dental is a fictional densitry firm that I created both a website and logo for.&lt;/p></content></item><item><title>Shibstop Logo</title><link>https://fearlessgeekmedia.com/portfolio/logos/shibstop/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://fearlessgeekmedia.com/portfolio/logos/shibstop/</guid><description>Shibstop Logo This is the Shibstop logo. Actually, you’ll notice two versions of the logo. One is just the S.
The S has ears. These are supposed to be the ears of a Shiba Inu dog. This is actually based on the Shiba Inu coin logo, which is shown below.
From what I’ve been told, I could have used the Shiba Inu logo with no problems, as the creator of the coin was anonymous and the code for the cryptocurrency is open source.</description><content>
&lt;figure class="center" >
&lt;img src="https://fearlessgeekmedia.com/portfolio-images/logos/shibstop_logo.png" style="border-radius: 8px; width:500px" />
&lt;figcaption class="center" >Shibstop Logo&lt;/figcaption>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://fearlessgeekmedia.com/portfolio-images/logos/shibstop_S.png" alt="Shibstop Logo S">&lt;/p>
&lt;p>This is the Shibstop logo. Actually, you’ll notice two versions of the logo. One is just the S.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The S has ears. These are supposed to be the ears of a Shiba Inu dog. This is actually based on the Shiba Inu coin logo, which is shown below.&lt;/p>
&lt;img src="https://fearlessgeekmedia.com/portfolio-images/logos/shiba-inu-logo.png" width="400"/>
&lt;p>From what I’ve been told, I could have used the Shiba Inu logo with no problems, as the creator of the coin was anonymous and the code for the cryptocurrency is open source. Supposedly this makes the image open source as well. However, I know it’s not true for all cryptocurrencies, and I could not find anything official about the Shiba Inu logo. So I created my own logo without the Shiba Inu logo, which is fine, because that’s just one more thing I can add to the portfolio! But you could easily see how the Shiba Inu logo could fit inside the S.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>On Facebook for the profile picture of the Shibstop page, I felt it was best just to use the S. I could see transitioning to just the S in the future as the logo for Shibstop rather than using the whole name.&lt;/p></content></item><item><title>Tryonian Chronicles Logo</title><link>https://fearlessgeekmedia.com/portfolio/logos/tryonianchronicles/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://fearlessgeekmedia.com/portfolio/logos/tryonianchronicles/</guid><description>Guardians fo Time Title Screen with Tryonian Chrnoicles Logo This is actually a loading screen for a computer roleplaying game I&amp;rsquo;m working on. The series is called Tryonian Chronicles, and the first game of the series will be called Guardians of Time.
The game itself takes place on a planet called Tryonius, which is an Earth-like planet but with three rings, and they have three other planets within their star system that are also habitable.</description><content>
&lt;figure class="center" >
&lt;img src="https://fearlessgeekmedia.com/portfolio-images/logos/GuardiansOfTime.png" style="border-radius: 8px; width:500px" />
&lt;figcaption class="center" >Guardians fo Time Title Screen with Tryonian Chrnoicles Logo&lt;/figcaption>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;p>This is actually a loading screen for a computer roleplaying game I&amp;rsquo;m working on. The series is called Tryonian Chronicles, and the first game of the series will be called Guardians of Time.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The game itself takes place on a planet called Tryonius, which is an Earth-like planet but with three rings, and they have three other planets within their star system that are also habitable. The game incorporates both sci-fi and fantasy elements.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Tryonius, being a three-ringed planet, is why we have the three-ringed planet in the logo.&lt;/p></content></item></channel></rss>